<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://alishahidi.net//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://alishahidi.net//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-11-04T20:06:04+00:00</updated><id>https://alishahidi.net//feed.xml</id><title type="html">Ali Shahidi</title><subtitle>I am a dedicated Java Software Developer with a strong passion for open-source projects. With extensive experience in developing and maintaining high-quality applications, I excel in problem-solving and optimizing code for performance. My technical skills include Java, Spring Boot, and various database technologies. I am committed to continuous learning and staying updated with industry trends, and I thrive in collaborative environments where I can contribute my expertise to create innovative solutions. In my free time, I enjoy exploring new technologies and participating in programming communities, always looking for ways to enhance my skills and knowledge. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to My Personal Blog</title><link href="https://alishahidi.net//blog/2024/welcome-to-my-personal-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to My Personal Blog"/><published>2024-11-04T09:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-11-04T09:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://alishahidi.net//blog/2024/welcome-to-my-personal-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://alishahidi.net//blog/2024/welcome-to-my-personal-blog/"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my blog! I’m excited to finally launch this space where I’ll be sharing insights, experiences, and ideas on topics that I’m passionate about. Writing has always helped me reflect and connect with others, and this blog is a way for me to dive deeper into these conversations.</p> <h4 id="why-im-starting-this-blog">Why I’m Starting This Blog</h4> <p>Starting a blog has been on my mind for a while. I want to document my journey, share knowledge, and connect with like-minded people who enjoy exploring new ideas. This blog is not only a place to share my thoughts but also a resource for those who might find value in the topics I cover.</p> <h4 id="topics-ill-cover">Topics I’ll Cover</h4> <ul> <li><strong>Tech &amp; Development</strong>: As a developer, I’ll be sharing tutorials, project insights, and the latest in web development. My goal is to create content that’s both useful and engaging.</li> <li><strong>Personal Growth</strong>: I believe in continuous improvement, and I’ll be sharing what I’ve learned about productivity, mindset, and other areas that have helped me grow.</li> <li><strong>Random Musings</strong>: Occasionally, I’ll write about things that catch my interest, even if they don’t fit into a specific category. Think of it as a space for creativity and exploration.</li> </ul> <h4 id="goals-for-this-blog">Goals for This Blog</h4> <ul> <li>To document my journey and share meaningful insights</li> <li>To create a resource that others can find valuable</li> <li>To build connections with people who share similar interests</li> </ul> <hr/> <blockquote> <p>“The journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step.”<br/> — Lao Tzu</p> </blockquote> <p>Thank you for stopping by, and I hope you’ll enjoy reading my posts as much as I enjoy writing them! Feel free to leave comments or reach out—I’d love to connect and hear your thoughts.</p> <p>Stay tuned for more!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog"/><category term="introduction"/><category term="personal"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to my blog, my journey, and what’s coming next.]]></summary></entry></feed>